http://www.hartinsurance.com/privacy-policy

Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Business Catastrophe Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Medical Payments Coverage
Choosing the right auto insurance is the key to keeping you and your car safe on the road in the event of an accident or other vehicle damage.
In-Home Business Insurance
Look after your biggest investment and everything in it with a proper policy that ensures its protection in the event of an accident or natural disaster.
Other Personal Insurance
Identity Theft
Personal Umbrella Insurance
Keep your confidential information and personal assets secure with extended coverage options including personal umbrella insurance.
Life Insurance
Individual Life Insurance
Group Life Insurance
Disability Insurance
Key Person (Key Men) Insurance
Provide your family with the security they deserve in the event of your passing with a life insurance policy that meets your financial and personal needs.
Health Insurance
Medicare
Individual & Family Health Insurance
Dental Coverage
Vision Coverage
Temporary Health Insurance
Disability Insurance
HSAs
Making good decisions today can secure a healthy tomorrow for you and your family with individual or group plans designed to meet your specifications.
Recreational Vehicle Insurance
Boat Insurance
Motorcycle Insurance
Motorhome Insurance
ATV Insurance
Snowmobile Insurance
Insure your freedom for adventure with a recreational vehicle policy that covers everything from your boat and RV to your ATV or motorcycle.
Additional Insurance Services
Special Event Insurance
Other Services
Wedding Insurance and Special Event Insurance
Take care of all your specialty insurance needs and other services with extended policy options for your convenience and satisfaction.
Coverage for Specific Industries
Accounting Firm Insurance
Alarm Contractors Insurance
Insurance for Arborists
Bar Insurance
Box Truck Insurance
Builders Risk Insurance
Car Dealership Insurance
Vineyard & Winery Insurance
Industry-specific risks make it impossible for insurance companies to lump together one insurance plan for every business.
Coverage for Your Business
Bonds
Business Catastrophe Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Commercial Auto Insurance
Commercial General Liability
Commercial Property Insurance
Commercial Real Estate Insurance
Commercial Umbrella Insurance
Crime Insurance
Cyber Liability Insurance
Equipment Insurance
Van Insurance
We’re committed to keeping your business protected so you can focus on your day-to-day operations.
Coverage for Your Employees
Group Benefits
Group Disability Insurance
Voluntary Benefits
Retiree Health Coverage
Group Health Insurance
Disability Insurance
Individual Life Insurance
We work hard to provide the best protection plans for businesses and their employees.
Farm Insurance
Crop Insurance
Farm Owners Insurance
Farm Equipment Insurance
Farm Dwelling Insurance
Farm Structures Insurance
Farm Auto Insurance
Farm Umbrella Insurance
Farm Liability Insurance
Preserve your livelihood with an agribusiness policy that safeguards your farm and everything on it, from buildings and machinery to crops and livestock.
Get A Quote
Contact Us
Grants Pass Office
Medford Office
Locations & Hours
Email Us
Call Us Today!
Call Grants Pass Office
Call Medford Office
Home
About
Our Staff
Our Locations
COVID-19 Notice
We Hart Local
Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Medical Payments Coverage
Home Insurance
Earthquake Insurance
Home & Auto Insurance
Property Insurance
Homeowners Liability
Renters Insurance
Condo Insurance
Business Catastrophe Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Commercial Auto Insurance
Commercial General Liability
Commercial Property Insurance
Commercial Real Estate Insurance
Commercial Umbrella Insurance
Crime Insurance
Cyber Liability Insurance
Equipment Insurance
Privacy Policy
We value you as a customer and respect your right to privacy. We know that you purchase our products and services because you trust that we stand behind our promises. We pledge our commitment to treat your information responsibly. We created this privacy policy to show you that we are working hard to protect your privacy.
Information sharing and opt out
We do not sell your personal information to anyone for any reason. We do not share it, except for the reasons described below, which are permitted by federal and state law. Therefore, there is no need for you to opt out. If we change our policy, we will tell you and give you a chance to opt out before we share your information.
Confidentiality and security
We use physical and technical safeguards to protect your information. We restrict access to your information to those who need it to perform their jobs. Third-party business partners are bound by law to use the information only for our purposes. They may not disclose it or use it in any other way. We comply with all data security laws.
Collecting your personal information
We collect personal information about you from different sources. For example, we collect information you send us on applications and forms. We also collect information from your transactions with our sister companies, others, or us. We may collect information from a consumer-reporting agency or a medical provider. This collection depends on the product or service you request.
Disclosing your personal information
We do not sell your information to anyone. We may disclose this information to a business that carries out services and marketing for us. We may disclose your information as required or permitted by law. We may disclose your information for a legal or regulatory purpose. These include the following types of information.
We may disclose information we receive from you on applications or other forms. This may include your name, address, beneficiaries, Social Security number and family member information. This may also include assets, income, and the property address and value.
We may disclose information from your transactions with our sister companies, or us. This may include your account balance, policy coverage, and payment history. This may also include premium paid, preferences, claims, and purchase method.
We may disclose information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency or other report. This may include, your credit report, motor vehicle and driver data. This may also include medical and employment data, loss history reports, and other driver data. This disclosure depends on the products you select.
We may disclose information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. As permitted by law, we may disclose some information to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.
Using your medical information
We sometimes must collect medical information to provide you a product or to pay a claim. We do not use or share it for any purpose, except the following:
Underwriting insurance
Administering your policy, account, or claim
As required or permitted by law
As otherwise authorized by you
Internet Policies
What information does Hart Insurance Agency collect from Web sites? Hart Insurance Agency may collect the information you provide when you:
Request information from the Hart Insurance Agency Web site
Use online tools and calculators
Apply online for products
Subscribe to online services
Complete an online form
Conduct transactions online
Apply for a job online
Hart Insurance Agency contracts with certain unaffiliated business partners who help us deliver online products and services. They may keep the information you provide. Other online activities are listed below.
Visitor Data
Hart Insurance Agency collects site-aggregate and customer-specific information about the pages you view on our site. We log IP addresses, browser and platform types, domain names, access times and referral data. We also collect information a customer volunteers on surveys and electronic forms. This information is used to improve our Web site.
Hart Insurance Agency gathers data on its Web site. This is a standard industry practice and is used to find out how visitors use our site. We collect aggregate information on the public areas of our Web site. We also collect information on an individual basis on areas of our Web site that require visitors to logon using an ID and password. We may collect the following data:
How many people visit our Web site
The pages they visit and the features they use
How long they stay on our Web site
The Web site people come from before reaching our Web site
Use of "Cookies"
We store a cookie on your computer when you visit our Web site. A cookie is a tiny piece of information that is required to create and maintain a secure session. Cookies let you request information and do business online. Cookies do not have confidential or personal information. They do not track a user after leaving our Web site. We use a third-party tracking utility, which may set cookies, to analyze how users move within our Web site.
Other Online Security
We also use a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). This keeps all information confidential when it is sent between our Web site and your computer.
E-mail
We keep the e-mail you send to us. If you agree to receive e-mail messages from us, we will keep the information you give us to send e-mail of specific interest to you. If you choose to send us e-mail, we keep your e-mail, your e-mail address, and our reply. Please be careful about the information you give us in e-mail. As with any public Web site, this communication may not be secure.
Web Links
It is important to note that other companies or organizations may have links on the Hart Insurance Agency family of Web sites. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or security of information by the companies or organizations outside of the Hart Insurance Agency family of companies. Please read the privacy policy of Web sites reached through the use of links from the Hart Insurance Agency family of Web sites.
Why does Hart Insurance Agency collect information on its Web site?
Hart Insurance Agency or our business partners use the information from our Web sites for many purposes:
Edits and feedback
Marketing and promotions
Analysis of user behavior
Product development
Content improvement
Informing advertisers how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements
Customize Web site content and layout
What happens if Hart Insurance Agency changes its privacy policy?
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on our homepage. This way you always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
If we decide to use your personal information in a different way than for the use that we told you when we collected it, we will notify you by posting a note on our Web site for 30 days.
Questions
We value our customers and want you to understand how we use the information we collect. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
We will provide you a copy of your personal information that we control and can reasonably retrieve. To access your information, you must provide the following:
All policy numbers you want to access.
Please sign your request and have your signature notarized. This ensures the identity of the person requesting the information.
We do not currently charge a fee to cover the cost of providing you with a copy of this information. However, we do reserve the right to charge a small fee in the future.
You may request that we correct your personal information in our files. Please note that we do not control information provided by third parties. So, you will need to contact the third party to correct any information from them.
Sometimes we obtain your consumer or credit report. If so, you may request the credit-reporting agency's name and address. You may ask the agency to give you a copy of your report.
Please send any inquiries to us at:
Hart Insurance Agency
ATTN: Privacy Department
321 SE I Street
Grants Pass, OR 97526
When you write to us, please include your name, address, and policy number, and your agent name and number, if you know it. You can contact your agent to change information that we control, such as your address. Or, you may contact your Hart Insurance Agency customer service representative. The phone number is in your policy packet.
This privacy statement describes our privacy practices for both current and former customers. We will provide one copy of this notice to joint policy or contract holders. Please share this information with everyone covered by your policy or contract. If you request, we will send more copies of this statement.
Thank you for choosing Hart Insurance Agency. We look forward to building a lifetime relationship with you.
Allied Property and Casualty Insurance Company
AMCO Insurance Company
Depositors Insurance Company
Nationwide Mutual Insurance Company
Nationwide Agribusiness Insurance Company
Colonial County Mutual Insurance Company
Our Locations
Grants Pass Office
Medford Office
1123 Royal Ave.
Medford, OR 97504
Main office: 541-779-4232
Fax: 541-772-3963
Get Directions
View All Locations
Our Providers
Testimonials
I would like to share with you the exceptional service I got from Heidi Lloyd over the last few months. She worked with me to get my car repaired after I damaged it. It was a horrible experience and I was not looking forward to dealing with insurance issues/claims and then a potential increase in premium, etc. Heidi made it all work smoothly and simply without a hitch. I could not have expected a better outcome. Following that ordeal, she answered all my questions about my auto policy increase and pursued getting my policy reevaluated which resulted in premium savings! She not only did an outstanding job in terms of efficiency, responsiveness and outcome, she has great customer service skills and was very personable. Your office has handled my insurance needs for decades and it’s always been super, but Heidi made it even better.
Sally
They go above and beyond for me here! Been with them for many years, and during that time they have saved my bacon dozens of times. Sometimes I goof on paperwork or payments, sometimes the insurance companies Hart sources from will make a mistake, and they always step up to help me. Working on an audit of premiums right now (3rd party audit company made a mistake), and Hart got with me immediately with all the steps I needed to take to resolve it. Wouldn't want to work with anyone else!
N. Rogers
Teri and the Hart Insurance team are always responsive and efficient! Whatever our insurance needs are, whether business or personal, Hart has been able to help in a quick and friendly way
H. Jack
I have used Hart insurance for many, many years. Part of that time I was employed as a public employee and they always handled our group insurance. After retiring, I have always used Hart In’s. to advise me with my Medicare options. They are professional, organized and eager to help.
L. Kellenbeck
Great company, fabulous people. I used Hart to help with personal and business insurance for many years. Then I switched for a slightly better price. Poor decision. I now have personal and business policies managed with Hart once again - and i won't switch! Terry Faulkner helps with the commercial; Sue Klumph deals with our personal home and vehicle insurance. I highly recommend Hart Insurance. You will not be disappointed.
J. Lefeber
Our business has been working with Hart Insurance for over a decade and they have been amazing to work with.
They handle all of our business insurance.
From year to year, they help us to reevaluate our needs and costs for insurance and represent a variety of carriers so I know that we are always getting the most competitive rates.
I have one point of contact there (Misty W) and she takes care of all of our needs so that we can continue to do what we do best....landscaping.
Using Hart Insurance is like pushing the "Easy" button.
We highly recommend them!
Xai G.
I spoke with Deanie yesterday for my son who was looking for car insurance. She went above and beyond helping him. Great people with great integrity. #1 in my book!
D. Murphy
Very attentive and work well for both my business and personal insurance needs. Best agents I've had in a long time!
Grants Pass, OR,
Medford, OR,
Rogue River, OR,
Ashland, OR,
Central Point, OR,
Jacksonville, OR,
and surrounding areas.
Licensed in OR, AK, AZ, CA, CO, ID, NV, UT and WA
Privacy | Site Map
